i just have not been interested in what is definitely the biggest story in hip-hop over
the weekend kendrick and drake all right so catch us up man catch us up some of the facts that were
dropped on this is kendrick was accused by drake of putting his hands on his fiance also accused
kendrick of living a double life and cheating on his fiance then kendrick accused drake of hiding
another child and having a secret daughter kendrick is also accusing drake of being a gambling addict a
drug addict a colonizer kendrick also says that drake has predators on his payroll which has kind
of been proven that one of drake's friends is up for alleged human traffic kendrick dropped all of
these back-to-back disc records within a matter of 72 hours that's what you missed so nothing i know
it was a lot going on it's just a lot of back and forth but i think some of the damage that has
been done to um drake's reputation might go beyond this you know what's so interesting is how he can
say all of that and be cheered on but when i voiced that a number of women had come into my comments
to name someone that had yeah harmed them that i was seen as a man hater and a rabble rouser and a liar
you didn't do it over a beat you should have done it over a beat you got me
you needed a beat
we are we are we are